[Music]
[Música]
and well the title track that you
y bueno el tema del título por el que
're all asking about no the test won't
todos estáis preguntando no el test no
talk about Dallas anymore I don't know if it gives me
hablará más de dallas no sé si me marca
a click Bale
un clic bale
if it gives me there's a clip with the title it's that it
si me marca hay un clip con el título es
turns it into the clip you see
que me lo convierte en el clip veis por
why because this one I haven't seen
qué porque éste sí que no lo he visto
this track okay I imagine is there really is
este tema vale me imagino hay de verdad
really Paulet let me start a
hay de verdad paulet déjame empezar un
video without them having to put the
vídeo sin que me tengan que poner los
stupid dicks on me then the same while in
tonto pollas luego el mismo mientras en
minutes 3 the beginning are dogs I don't know
minutos 3 el principio son perros no sé
what I don't know how much let me live
qué no sé cuánto déjame vivir
by the way his little mustache hey guys
por cierto su bigotito oye los chicos
my texts lately do you remember
los textos míos últimamente os acordáis
that I haven't thrown away the red wine
que no tiraba el tinto
lately listen to me or that I had a
últimamente escúchame o que tenía un
text with 50,000 views
texto con 50.000 visitas
follow me on Christ today I hope because
me seguís en cristo hoy espero porque de
suddenly there's a lot of vtv you are michat
repente hay un montón de vtv eres michat
dark and knicks vtv but leave the roll
dark y knicks vtv pero dejarme el rollo
to me it's good to see listen to me the chip
a mí es bueno ver escúchame los chip
being on seen their triples giving in
estando en visto sus triples dando en
titles and lending in urging that the
títulos y prestando en instar a que los
triple so much everywhere continue
triple tanto en todos lados seguir
lying continue  meditate on milestone roll is
mentido seguir meditar a hito rollo
worthless it's thanks to the
vale de nada es gracias al apoyo en
moral support that we give you paulillo well no
moral que te damos paulillo pues no
paulo the truth is that there is none I don't believe it
paulo la verdad que no hay de no lo creo
well this dog [ __ ] context the
bueno este perro al [__] contexto el
dead has commented on the subject willy against
dead ha comentado el tema willy contra
grave some platform companions
grave algunos compañeros de plataforma
have used the beige click about that in
han utilizado el clic beige sobre que en
some part of the video he says that he will not
alguna parte del vídeo dice que no
talk more about dallas the fact is that
hablará más de dallas el caso es que
this is not true the grandfather will mark
esto no sea cierto el abuelo se marcará
a click bait in the same way and we will go up
un clic bait de igual forma y subiremos
to press be his reaction to see that he
a pulsar sea su reacción al ver que
will have to do it greetings
tendrá que hacerlo un saludo
I can't take these surprises
yo no puedo llevarme estas sorpresas en
live man if I hire jce to
directo tío si yo contrato para que me
prepare me a little the subject trusting
prepare jce un poco el tema confiando en
you while I am busy
ustedes mientras que yo estoy ocupado
with other things I can't suddenly
por otras cosas yo no puedo de repente
find myself live with well we don't
encontrarme en directo con de bueno no
know we don't know what the [ __ ] or
sabemos no sabemos de qué [__] o te va a
this extract is going to be about but we have read in
tratar este extracto pero hemos leído en
some titles that the one mentioned the in
algunos títulos que el de mencionada la
between or rather this could be the
por medio o sea que esto puede ser el
clip made the clip bay of the clip of the clip
clip made el clip bay del clip del clip
mail that you have eaten the
mail que ustedes hayan comido el club
gay club you have put it to me and I put
gay me la habéis puesto a mí y yo ponga
a dry climate more is in decline of your
un clima seco más está en declive de su
house thank you very much it has been for the  prime
casa muchas gracias ha sido por el prime
attentively paula and so you don't
atentamente paula y para que no te
get angry
enojes
for
para
[Music]
[Música]
what
qué
and
e
this
esto
the highest sweet
el altísimo dulce
to save today don't give it another thought
para ahorrar hoy no le des más vueltas
go to simyo with your eyes closed
pásate a simyo con los ojos cerrados
create your own rate and change it whenever
crea tu propia tarifa y cambiarla cuando
you want
quieras
choose simyo and save you
elige simyo y ahorra
have to put a stop I'm talking I
tiene que poner punto hablo
'm going to have to put a stop I'm talking
voy a tener que poner punto hablo
this is direct here a point here
esto es lo directo aquí un punto acá
many things without desire in his life but
muchas cosas sin ganas en su vida pero
well willy seems to be worth seeing those
pues a willy como que le valen ver esas
things it's not more like well this is the
cosas no es más como pues yo esta es la
impression that I had with grefa at the
impresión que yo tuve con grefa en su
time this is what I know of him and they
momento es lo que conozco de él y ya
were already team publications
estaban equipo publicaciones
also apart there is this or rather there is
también aparte está esto o sea está el
him the one
él
that apart from willy it is noticeable that
el que a parte willy se nota que
they put a disagreement with well
pusieron una disconformidad con pues
working with grecia and I think that is
trabajar con grecia y eso creo que es
something normal in the end he is a person and
algo normal al final de es una persona y
not everyone is going to be fine and you know
ya no todos se van a quedar bien y sabes
if we go but in the end what we talked about
si vamos pero al final lo que hablamos
if you have a disagreement about working
si tienes una disconformidad de trabajar
with greg never work with serious what the
con greg no trabajen nunca con grave qué
hell are you doing in a series where  there are 24
[__] haces en una serie donde estáis 24
youtubers streamer among which is the
youtubers streamer entre los que está el
serious
grave
stupidity you know that you are going to cross paths with it
estupidez sabes que te vas a cruzar con
can even fall on your
es que te puede caer incluso en tu
team
equipo
but the thing is that then they call him for
pero es que luego lo llaman para
collaborations of energy drinks and
colaboraciones de bebidas energéticas y
there they take pictures the two together and
ahí se hacen fotitos los dos juntitos y
not that they take pictures the two together it
no que se hagan fotitos los dos juntitos
is that surely the two of them were
es que seguramente hayan estado los dos
alone there every day doing the
solos allí todos los días haciendo la
photo shoot and they will have to be
sesión de fotos y habrá que estar los
both there in good vibes and it will have been
dos allí de buen rollo y habrá estado
good with him in view of the day okay
bien con él de cara al echar día vale
maybe it is as I tell you at his serious moment
tal vez es como te digo en su momento
of a bad impression on Willy
de una mala impresión a willy
and I am uy that stayed with this image
y estoy uy que se quedó por esta imagen
that well this guy is a taxi driver said that it is
de que pues este güey es taxista decía
wrong it is wrong to do this but
que está mal está mal hacer esto pero
well that is how people are that is how we are
pues así así es la gente así es así
humans
somos los humanos
we judge if we have this idea that if
juzgamos si tenemos esta idea de que si
someone did something at some point like that
alguien hizo algo en algún momento así
that person is in three I do
esa persona está en tres
n't know or the same and they don't know each other a
no sé o sea igual y no se conocen un
little more maybe Willis also because he
poquito más igual willis además porque
thinks like why or why he
piensa así como por qué o por qué él
prefers to get away from serious and his
prefiere como que alejarse de grave y su
group of friends but well that is the
grupo de amigos pero pues eso
same to see in the end of this
igual a ver al final de esto
neither one nor  another is affected their
ni a uno ni a otro le afecta sus cuentas
bank accounts are very good so they flew
de banco están muy bien así que volaban
from the signal
de la señal
you
ustedes
or well the people who are fans of Greece or
o bueno la gente que sea fan de grecia
Willy
de willy
to defend one another because believe me
a defender a uno al otro porque créanme
none of the others are affected in
que a ninguno de los otros les afecta en
any way whether they get along well or bad nothing
ninguna manera que se lleven bien o mal
in the cafe is affecting them but man
nada en el café están afecte pero hombre
action subject that has given that speaks a lot
acción tema que ha dado que habla mucho
because the truth is ugly you up
porque la verdad está feo te hasta el
front I this week I have to make a
frente yo esta semana tengo que hacer un
powerful video that we are preparing
vídeo potente que estamos preparando
we are finishing compiling okay a
estamos terminando de recopilar vale un
powerful video about the whole
vídeo potente sobre sobre toda la
history the storytime of life in
historia el storytime de la vida de
fact both are going very well it
hecho los dos le van muy bien
is not mandatory to get along with
no es obligatorio llevarte bien con
someone unfortunately people do not
alguien desafortunadamente la gente no
understand this on the internet
entiende esto en internet
someone can screw me at the same time no matter how much of a
a mí me puede [__] alguien la vez
public figure I am I can
por más figura pública que soy yo puedo
publicly say this person I do not
públicamente decir esta persona no me
like even sorry but there are people that I do
cae bien hasta perdón pero hay gente que
not like and the reasons perhaps would
no me cae bien y ya las razones tal vez
not need to be said in the case
no se necesitarían decirlo en el caso
as I tell you with people that I do not like,
como les digo con personas que me caen
there are people that I do not like, there are
mal a mí hay gente que me cae mal hay
people that have said that I do not like but I do not
gente que dicho que me cae mal pero no
give them reasons because it is not necessary to
les doy razones porque no es necesario
create that is to the pse or neither
crear ese es al pse o tampoco
is it simply okay I do not like  to
simplemente es vale no me cae bien a
this person if one day they ask me
esta persona si algún día me preguntan
why I'm not working with this
por qué no estoy trabajando con esta
person well it's because I don't like him and you
persona pues es porque no me cae bien y
know
ya sabes
but there are also people who take it to
pero también hay gente que lo lleva a
another level and it's defending or
otro nivel y es estar defendiendo o
attacking youtubers you know you're at the
atacando youtubers lo sabah estás a la
part that you have put clubs in me of
parte que me habéis metido clubes de lo
the gal to not defending attacking people
del gal a no defendiendo atacando gente
no already by the way I'm at 60 fps and I don't
no ya por cierto estoy a 60 fps y eso no
like that
me gusta
ah
ah
[ __ ] mother
[__] madre
already
ya de gol
with him he
con él
keeps talking I do
sigue hablando
n't know who was bigger [ __ ] he's bad
no sé quién era más [__] es malo
and
y
you know it seems like it's in fashion and I
sabes que parece que está de moda y
'm talking last week but it
estoy hablamos la semana pasada pero
seems like it's in fashion that people
parece que está de moda que la gente
want to mess with who takes
quiera meterse con quién se lleva a
someone with whom you don't know but that you
alguien con quien no sabes pero que le
believe that coming affects you it
crees que vengas te afecta a ti
means william wiley year surpassed
significa william wiley año superó
that not that it affects but if they have done it
que no que afecte pero si lo han hecho
in a tournament and there is a seat left it is
en un torneo y ya queda un asiento se
uncomfortable in a tournament we
incomoda en un torneo
can discuss it do not be plans
podemos comentarlo no sean plans se
things are talked about no neither of
hablan las cosas se hablan no ninguno de
the two neither one nor the one nor the other to be
los dos ni uno ni el uno ni el otro para
happy
felices
as greg says well it was not there it was
como dice greg pues no estaba ha sido
because it was an event between compass it was
porque era un evento entre compás era
for the good vibes etcetera but  Well, in the
por el buen rollo etcétera pero pues al
end, he doesn't believe he can control what
final de tampoco cree puede controlar lo
another person did, you know, also
que hizo otra persona sabes también
Greece, as he says, he has uploaded several
grecia como dice él ha cargado varias
times
veces
and I think that in addition, any person
y creo que está además cualquier persona
in general
en general
wanting to correct what another person says,
querer corregir lo que otra persona dice
base has already been uploaded, they should not
base ya se ha cargado no se deben dar
realize because if they don't realize, then
cuenta porque si no se dan cuenta pues
in the end it is useless.
al final no sirve de nada
But well, thank you David, thank you for
pero bueno yo gracias david gracias por
the people, thank you
la gente gracias
also for the fight between Wild Wild and
además para la pelea entre wild wild and
Wesson,
wesson
for example, speaking of the widget,
por ejemplo hablando del widget
this has had dogs with half the world
esto ha tenido perros con medio mundo
also in the zombie community,
también de que en la comunidad de
but he has also remained as if
pero él también se ha mantenido como que
in his own thing, you know, like, he doesn't
en su propio rollo sabes en plan no se
want to lose weight. Now this content
quiere adelgazar ahora este contenido
stops being content and
deja de ser contenido
returns to being content. He has had his
regresa a ser contenido ha tenido sus
arguments with these people with others
discusiones con estas personas con otras
that the truth is that the guy
que la verdad el bato
used to watch it when I was
antes lo veía cuando cuando era más
younger on YouTube and that,
pequeño en youtube y eso
but to collaborate, I never felt like
pero para colaborar nunca me dio ganas
asking him for collaboration
de pedirle colaboración
because why,
por qué
but I did notice that the cat was more
pero si notaba como que el gato era más
distant, you know,
alejado sabes
if I ever noticed that,
si llegaba a notar eso
come with this, those those guys are
que venga con esto esos esos güeyes son
real, what I can do,
reales lo que puedo
well, in the stratum
pues en el estrato
[Music]
[Música]
in the ninth stadium, mark dances
en el estadio novena marca bailes
in the extractor, I'm not going to put him to
en el extractor no le voy a poner a
do much, if he did  good content
hacer mucho si hiciera contenido bueno
if it had been with its most
si hubiera sido con su contenido más
constant content and I feel very good in the
constante y siento muy bien en el
stratum I'm not going to put by you
estrato no voy a poner by simplemente
can simply give your opinion on asking for a
puedes opinar de lo de pedir una opinión
very vague opinion not only has the one here been left like this a
muy vaga no sólo ha quedado el de aquí
super super super vague opinion
así una opinión súper súper súper vaga
like this a super vague opinion and an opinion
así una opinión super vaga y una opinión
is that they have put have
es que hayan puesto
put something gala I don't know if it has
hayan puesto algo de gala no sé si ha
been the one about loves no
sido la de amores no
since with him of that [ __ ] that
ya que con él de esa [__] esa [__]
[ __ ] catchy [ __ ] has already arrived the one of if it has
[__] pegadiza ya llegó el de si ha
been nothing the putting
sido nada la puesta
nothing nor weapon go click down and give it to him
nada ni arma vaya clic baja y se la da
the one of not talking
el de no hablar a de dallas asiladas la
about Dallas asylums the one who has put literally I don't know I don't know or rather the one of if he had to mention Dallas it seems that he liked or disliked it is that he is in the first place I don't think that the one of would have a problem in saying if he likes or dislikes Dallas and
si le queda bien o mal en dallas y en
secondly
segundo lugar
saying that you like or dislike a person
decir que una persona te cae bien o mal
once they had their had their topic no
una vez tuvieron su tuvieron su tema no
he is ready the videos in the past of
él está listo los vídeos en el pasado de
him trying to get close to Dallas to
él intentó arrimarse a dallas para
stay it will help him grow or for him to advise him
quedar le ayudará a crecer o para que le
anyway anyway but what a clip of the data
en fin en fin pero vaya clip de la data
[Music]
[Música]